Hi!
Our next step is going to be cleaning the microwave oven rack.
This is going to be the same process as cleaning the turn table.
Let me get this wet first.
Spray that down.
Then just use your mild dish soap that you would use for cleaning your dishes and silverware.
You're going to wipe this down.
As I mentioned earlier, in general, you should not leave the rack in the microwave.
First of all, this helps prevent it from getting dirty.
Secondly, because it is metal, while it's made to use in your microwave, it can still cause problems, so you want to not use it, not leave it in there as much as possible.
Also, you want to make sure that when you're cleaning this, you're particularly careful about cleaning corners where it's going to be touching the microwave walls.
All of this will be in your microwave owner's manual.
You just want to make sure and get this all nice and clean.
Even if you keep this in your microwave most of the time, it probably still won't get that dirty unless you've got exploding food all the time.
This should be one of the easier steps.
We're just going to rinse it off and then put it to the side to dry.